http://www.concretesoftware.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Updated July 10, 2020
Concrete Software (“we”, “us” or “our”) is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizes your need for protection and management of any information (Personal and non-personal information) we collect when you use the mobile, online and downloadable products and services (“Services”) we offer.
To address this, Concrete Software has created this Privacy Policy so that our users can understand the care and respect with which we intend to treat your information as data controller. Our goal is always to create the best possible games and entertainment experiences. To do this, we need to understand our players’ behavior within our games and support our titles by serving appropriate advertisements. That said, we feel that your rights to privacy should always come first. In the spirit of transparency, this Privacy Policy outlines what information Concrete Software and its third party partners collect, how it is used, and your rights with regard to your own information.
This Privacy Policy applies to all of our games in which Concrete Software is the publisher, whether you play on mobile devices or other platforms, and sites. It also applies to our advertising activities on all platforms and other services that we may provide. By using our products, you consent to this policy. By using our products and services, you consent to this policy.
By downloading, accessing and/or playing our games, visiting our sites or using our other products, you consent to the collection of your information by us. We reserve the right to change our practices and this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the  updated version to our website and link to it in our games. We may also send an email or provide notice within some or all of our Services when this Privacy Policy changes. Each time a user accesses our Services, the Platform or 3rd Party Platform Games, the then current version of the Privacy Policy applies, and you agree that the information we collect will be subject to the Privacy Policy, as updated. We encourage you to check this page regularly so that you know our current practices.
We ask that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you have any questions or concerns after reading this, please contact us at support@concretesoftware.com.
Information We Collect
By downloading, accessing and/or playing our games, visiting our sites or using our other products, we may collect Information about you from you and other sources. The personal data we collect depends on the circumstances and the games and services you are using. Most of this data comes directly from you or your device, such as device information, country and region, and game play information. We use this data to provide our games and services to you, including for the purposes of optimization, preventing fraud, customizing in-game offers, verifying purchases, and providing technical support.
Information You Provide You provide certain personally identifiable information that uniquely identifies you such as:
Email address when you choose to participate in various activities on the Platform such as registering an account, sending feedback, entering sweepstakes and contests, responding to surveys;
Username to protect your account;
Information requested by us when you report a problem with our services;
Your contact information if you reach out to us;
Postal address and limited and tokenized payment information may be collected when uploading a game, or making a purchase; and/or
Other information to us directly or through third-party services.
You may also provide us information in the following manner:
Information you provide via Apps. You can choose to add information to your game profile or to connect our product to your account with a third party network (such as Facebook). If you do this, then your personal information, gameplay, and statistics will be visible to other players and we may also use it for the other purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Please make sure your privacy settings reflect your preferences.
Information through Social Media. Information that you post voluntarily now or in the future through our mobile, online, and downloadable products, or on an area of a social network monitored by us (e.g., our Facebook page) may be visible to others and collected by third-parties. Information that you disclose, including, but not limited to, through our online chat rooms, forums, game comments, profile shouts and direct messages are public and will be accessible to anyone who uses our Platform and/or 3rd Party Platform Games.
Information We Automatically Collect. We collect other information automatically when you use our products, including:
IP address;
Mobile and other hardware or device identifiers;
Browser information, including your browser type and the language you prefer;
Referring and exit pages, including landing pages and pages viewed;
Platform type;
Information about your media, device, hardware and software, such as your hardware settings and components, our software and updates you have installed or use, and presence of required plug-ins;
Details about which of our Services you use and how you use them; and
Device event information, including crash reports, request and referral URL’s and system activity details (e.g. whether you encountered an error playing our games or lost Internet access).
We also may collect and store information locally on your device, using mechanisms like cookies, browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.
Mobile Platforms. If you play or purchase our games on your mobile device and/or tablet, we receive information about you from the app stores and other mobile platform providers. This information includes your username and/or device ID and the fact that you made a purchase, for instance, but does not include any sensitive or financial information. Some of our mobile platforms also may send information to us that you authorize them to provide.
Information provided to us by third parties: Our games and sites may include advertising for third party products and services. By accepting this Privacy Policy and downloading or continuing to play our games or use our Services, you consent to us and our partners collecting and using information about you to improve advertising, targeting and measurement systems so that we can show you relevant third party ads in our games. Unless you opt out as explained below, we and our third party partners use information collected about you primarily to help us deliver relevant advertising to you.
A representative list of these types of third parties can be found below. We also may use information from third parties, for instance, to help us understand your approximate geolocation via your IP address for tax purposes, or to customize certain services to your location, and for fraud and/or abuse prevention purposes.
Third Party Providers
This table summarizes our ad serving and analytics providers and where you can go to get more information about their policies and practices and opt-out of their networks in many cases.
Network
Info
Opt-Out
AdColony
http://adcolony.com/legal/privacy/
https://www.adcolony.com/privacy-policy/#datarequests
AdMob
http://www.admob.com/home/privacy
http://www.google.com/settings/ads
AerServ
https://www.aerserv.com/privacy-policy/
https://www.aerserv.com/gdpr-data-subject-rights/#
Facebook
https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen
Flurry
http://www.flurry.com/privacy-policy.html
https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do
Google Analytics
http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/
privacyoverview.html
http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
InMobi
Amazon
https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010
https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=200127470
Oath
https://policies.oath.com/xw/en/oath/privacy/enterprise/
b2bprivacypolicy/
https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/
dashboard/index.html
IronSource
https://developers.ironsrc.com/ironsource-mobile/air/ironsource-mobile-privacy-policy/
CrossInstall
http://www.crossinstall.com/privacy/
http://www.crossinstall.com/data-subject-rights
How We Collect Information and How We Use it
Cookies: Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other widely-used tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Website activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Website.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Website and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
Analytic Technologies: We use our own game servers and internal and third party analytic technologies to collect user data from our games to improve game experience and stability.
Game Service
Details
HockeyApp
Collects information from your device to help diagnose and correct critical issues, such as game crashes
Google Analytics with Firebase
Collects information from application and device to understand game use
Unity Analytics
Collects information from application and device to understand game use
Flurry
Collects information from application and device to understand game use
Facebook Analytics
Collects information from application and device to understand game use
Customer Support: We use a third party support tool to collect Information through customer support to help troubleshoot issues and restore save data.
Support Service
Details
Zendesk
Collects email to respond to support inquiries
With Whom We Share Your Information
If you choose to provide us with your Information, we may transfer that Information within Concrete Software or Concrete Software’s third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country of jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.
Concrete Software strives to comply with all applicable laws around the world (including GDPR) that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Concrete Software intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In general, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is obtained, transferred, or retained.
We do not control information sent from your browser to third parties, such as advertising networks and analytics companies that receive information in the normal course of your Internet activity. When third party technologies or social tools are integrated into our products, those third parties may collect information when you use our products. An example is the Facebook “Like” button.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
We are committed to privacy. Protecting your privacy is an evolving area, and Concrete Software’s games and sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. Wherever your Information may be held within Concrete Software or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure. While we strive to take all appropriate measures to protect your information, we are not able to 100% guarantee the security of your information and we do not assume responsibility for the unauthorized use, access, or disclosure of your information.
Children
Protecting children’s privacy is extremely important to Concrete Software. Our games and services are intended for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the required age, please contact us via email here:  support@concretesoftware.com
Your Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Concrete Software. As a user of our software, you have the right to receive the data we collect and you may request that we delete that data at any time. If you decide to play the game after your personal information has been deleted, you may lose your save data. If you choose to start playing the game again , we collect new data from you as a user.
If you choose to have a relationship with Concrete Software, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
The Right to Request Deletion
You have the right to request that your personal information be deleted.  You also have the right to inform us that you do not wish us to sell personal information collected to third parties.  In order to make those requests, please contact us via email here:  support@concretesoftware.com or opt-out on a third party provider’s website.
